deandeluca.com 2014-11-23

# Dean & DeLuca - Privacy

**Updated April 2012  
**  
DEAN & DELUCA is committed to respecting your privacy and providing you proper protection and management of any Personally Identifiable Information you choose to share with us. Personally Identifiable Information consists of any information by which you can be personally identified or contacted, such as your first and last name, home or other physical address (including street name and name of a city or town), telephone number or e-mail address.

Your privacy is important to us. DEAN & DELUCA will not sell, share, or rent your Personally Identifiable Information to third parties in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

## [ Collecting Your Information ](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Privacy.aspx# "Expand/Collapse")

DEAN & DELUCA collects information from you at several different points on our Web site in order to facilitate the delivery of services or the fulfillment of an order. We may collect your IP address to analyze trends and customer interests as well as to administer the site, track your site movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to Personally Identifiable Information.

There will be times, such as when placing an order, subscribing to a service, registering on the site, registering to receive catalogs, participating in promotions, surveys and contests, at which we may request personal information such as your name, billing/shipping address, telephone number, e-mail address, credit card information, etc. It is solely your choice whether or not you provide this information. However, should you choose not to provide the information, we may be unable to process an order, fulfill a service, or display certain content on our Web site.

DEAN & DELUCA has arranged with PowerReviews, Inc. (d/b/a Buzzillions) ("PowerReviews") to facilitate the collection of customer product reviews on products sold by DEAN & DELUCA. When you submit a product review to DEAN & DELUCA, you are also subject to PowerReviews terms of use and privacy policies (see http://www.buzzillions.com/public/legal/index_en_US.html). Accordingly, you should review those policies prior to submitting a review. Also, reviews you submit may be posted on both http://www.Buzzillions.com and our site.

We may use third-party service providers to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our Web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over, but not your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of interest to you. This information is collected through the use of pixel tags or cookies. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, you can visit http:/www.networkadvertising.org/.

## [Using Your Information](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Privacy.aspx# "Expand/Collapse")

We use the Personally Identifiable Information you provide for internal purposes such as:  
analyzing trends and statistics

  * member services including Web page personalizationorder
  * history and status
  * one-click orderingorder confirmation and tracking
  * subscription services
  * informing you of new products, services, offers and information about DEAN & DELUCA.

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We may use outside purveyors to ship orders directly, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. In connection with these services, it is necessary to share certain Personally Identifiable Information with such providers. We have informed these companies that they are not to retain, share, store or use Personally Identifiable Information for any secondary purposes.

We may also share personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties if (1) you request or authorize it, (2) the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you as described above, (3) the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our terms of use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety, or the rights, property or safety of our users or others, (4) the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of the company or any of its services or assets (e.g., in the event that we sell assets to another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets), or (5) the information is provided to such third parties as otherwise described in this privacy policy.

At times, we partner with third parties to provide specific services, such as the mailing of our newsletters. When you sign up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. We have informed these parties that they are not allowed to use Personally Identifiable Information except for the purpose of providing these services.

We occasionally make our list of customer names and street addresses available to carefully screened companies and organizations whose product and activities might be of interest to you.To be removed from the list of persons whose information is shared with third parties, please send an e-mail to [customercare@deandeluca.com](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Feedback.aspx) or call 800.221.7714. You may also write to:

DEAN & DELUCA  
Attn: Customer Care

2526 E. 36th Street Circle North

Wichita, KS 67219

We also may share your Personally Identifiable Information and non-personal information, including your name, address, email address and any transactions you conduct on our website or offline with us with a third party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver tailored advertising to you that match your interests when you visit our website as well as other websites. Our advertising partner will make the data that we provide anonymous so that no one else will receive your Personally Identifiable Information.

## [California Privacy rights](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Privacy.aspx# "Expand/Collapse")

Under California law, California residents who have an established business relationship with a company may choose to opt out of disclosing personal information to third parties for marketing purposes.

We use the Personally Identifiable Information you provide for internal purposes such as:  
analyzing trends and statistics

  * member services including Web page personalization
  * order history and status
  * one-click ordering
  * order confirmation and tracking
  * subscription services
  * informing you of new products, services, offers and information about DEAN & DELUCA.

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We may use outside purveyors to ship orders directly, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services.In connection with these services, it is necessary to share certain Personally Identifiable Information with such providers. We have informed these companies that they are not to retain, share, store or use Personally Identifiable Information for any secondary purposes.

At times, we partner with third parties to provide specific services, such as the mailing of our newsletters. When you sign up for these services, we will share names, or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. We have informed these companies that they are not to retain, share, store or use Personally Identifiable Information for any secondary purposes.

We may also share personally identifiable information with unaffiliated third parties if (1) you request or authorize it, (2) the information is provided to help complete a transaction for you as described above, (3) the information is provided to comply with the law, applicable regulations, court orders or subpoenas, to enforce our terms of use or other agreements, or to protect our rights, property or safety, or the rights, property or safety of our users or others, (4) the disclosure is done as part of a purchase, transfer or sale of the company or any of its services or assets (e.g., in the event that we sell assets to another party, customer information may be one of the transferred assets), or (5) the information is provided to such third parties as otherwise described in this privacy policy.

We occasionally make our list of customer names and street addresses available to carefully screened companies and organizations whose product and activities might be of interest to you. To be removed from the list of persons whose information is shared with third parties, please send an e-mail to [customercare@deandeluca.com](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Feedback.aspx) or call 800.221.7714. You may also write to:

DEAN & DELUCA  
Attn: Customer Care

2526 E. 36th Street Circle North

Wichita, KS 67219

We also may share your Personally Identifiable Information and non-personal information, including your name, address, email address and any transactions you conduct on our website or offline with us with a third party advertising partner and its service providers in order to deliver tailored advertising to you that match your interests when you visit our website as well as other websites. Our advertising partner will make the data that we provide anonymous so that no one else will receive your Personally Identifiable Information.

Effective date of this privacy policy is April 10, 2012

## [Updating Your Information](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Privacy.aspx# "Expand/Collapse")

At any time you may review, update, correct, or change the Personally Identifiable Information you have provided to us. You may also choose to no longer receive any communication from DEAN & DELUCA, however you may continue to receive communications from those companies we shared your information with prior to your notification to us. You may use our Web site, through the My Account pages, to change your information. Alternatively, you can e-mail us at [customercare@deandeluca.com](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Feedback.aspx), or call us 800.221.7714.

You may also write to us at:

DEAN & DELUCA  
Attn: Customer Care

2526 E. 36th Street Circle North

Wichita, KS 672198

## [Web Cookies](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Privacy.aspx# "Expand/Collapse")

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user.

We use cookies to identify one user from another and to track marketing promotions and apply promotional discounts. The cookies contain no Personally Identifiable Information. As our shopping cart functionality requires the use of cookies to function, you will not be able to make purchases on our site if you have disabled cookies in your browser. Once you close your browser, the cookie expires.

## [Links](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Privacy.aspx# "Expand/Collapse")

This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that DEAN & DELUCA is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects Personally Identifiable Information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

## [Member Services](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Privacy.aspx# "Expand/Collapse")

In order to set up an account with DEAN & DELUCA, you must first complete the registration form. During registration, you are required to give your contact information (such as name and e-mail address). This information may be used to contact you about the services on our site for which you have expressed interest, such as Web page personalization, order history and status.

## [Catalog Mailing List](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Privacy.aspx# "Expand/Collapse")

If you wish to subscribe to our catalog mailing list, we ask for contact information such as name and street address. We occasionally make our list of customer names and street addresses available to carefully screened companies and organizations whose product and activities might be of interest to you.To be removed from the list of persons whose information is shared with third parties, please send an e-mail to [customercare@deandeluca.com](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Feedback.aspx) or call 800.221.7714. You may also write to:

DEAN & DELUCA  
Attn: Customer Care

2526 E. 36th Street Circle North

Wichita, KS 67219

You may continue to receive communications from those companies we shared your information with prior to your notification to us. Please note that because some mailings are prepared far in advance, allow up to 90 days for your request to be effective. We also honor all opt-out requests from DMAChoice.org.

## [Email List](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Privacy.aspx# "Expand/Collapse")

If you wish to receive e-mail notifications from us about products, services and promotions, we ask for contact information such as name and e-mail address. To be removed from our e-mail list, please click [opt-out](http://links.mkt265.com/ui/modules/display/optOut.jsp?f=38103&m=739794&r=OTEzNDI3NDQ1S0&j=NDI2MjE2MzMS1&mt=1)or send an e-mail to [customercare@deandeluca.com](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Feedback.aspx) or call 800.221.7714. You may also write to:

DEAN & DELUCA  
Attn: Email Opt-Out  
2402 E. 37th Street North  
Wichita, KS 67219

## [ Surveys & Contests](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Privacy.aspx# "Expand/Collapse")

From time-to-time our site requests information from you via surveys. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and shipping address), and demographic information (such as zip code, age level). Survey information will be used for purposes of monitoring or improving the use and satisfaction of this site.

We will share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

We occasionally make our list of customer names and street addresses available to carefully screened companies and organizations whose product and activities might be of interest to you.To be removed from the list of persons whose information is shared with third parties, please send an e-mail to [customercare@deandeluca.com](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Feedback.aspx) or call 800.221.7714. You may also write to:

DEAN & DELUCA  
Attn: Marketing  
2402 E. 37th Street North  
Wichita, KS 67219

## [ Special Offers](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Privacy.aspx# "Expand/Collapse")

We send all new members a welcoming e-mail to verify password and username. Established members will occasionally receive information on products, services, special offers, and a newsletter. Out of respect for your privacy, we present the option to not receive these types of communications in every e-mail. You may also email [customercare@deandeluca.com](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Feedback.aspx) or call 800.221.7714 at any time.

## [Security](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Privacy.aspx# "Expand/Collapse")

This Web site takes precautions to protect your information.

When our registration/order form asks you to enter sensitive information (such as credit card number), that information is encrypted and is protected with the customary encryption software used in the ecommerce industry - SSL.

## [ Notification of Policy Changes](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Privacy.aspx# "Expand/Collapse")

If we decide to make material changes to our privacy policy, in whole or in part, we will inform you by posting a notice on our Web site.Those changes will go into effect on the date posted in the notice. The new policy will apply to all current and past users of our web site and will replace any prior policies that are inconsistent. The effective date of the current privacy policy is April 10, 2012.

## [ Questions/Feedback](http://www.deandeluca.com/CustomerCare/Privacy.aspx# "Expand/Collapse")

If you have any questions about the privacy or security at our Web site, you can send an e-mail to [customercare@deandeluca.com.](mailto:customercare@deandeluca.com.)
